moderncommerce.com 2013-11-24

# Modern Commerce | Privacy Policy

We understand that the protection of your privacy is something that you take into consideration before using a website. Modern Commerce understands the need to ensure the protection of your privacy. We have designed this policy with our users in mind. This policy, along with the Terms Of Use, delegate how your information is being used and what steps we have taken to protect your personal information. If you cannot agree to the terms and conditions found in these policies, please abstain from using Modern Commerce.

**What we collect**

  * Name 
  * E-mail address 
  * Other information relevant to help you find special offers based on your interests and preferences 

**What does Modern Commerce do with your information?**

  * Record keeping. 
  * Makes improvements to our website to better serve you. 
  * Personalizes the website according to your preferences. 
  * Provides your information to third party affiliates so that advertisements you see are targeted toward your interests. 
  * If you choose to receive communications from us, occasional emails may be sent to you with special offers and/or newsletters. 
  * We will never sell your personal information.

**What We Do With Your Information**

  * Develop content and advertisements geared towards your preferences
  * Deliver you with high-quality customer service
  * Provide you with information based upon your interests
  * Find you online services based upon your needs
  * Recordkeeping

If you decide to opt-out of our mailing list and no long receive future emails or communications from Modern Commerce, you can do so by going to [http://www.moderncommerce.com/unsubscribe](http://www.serviceanswers.com/unsubscribe "http://www.serviceanswers.com/unsubscribe"). Enter your email address on this page and you will officially be unsubscribed.

**Will you ever sell my information?**

Third party products or services may be displayed on our site. These sites are independently owned and their privacy policy follows as such. We retain no liability or responsibility for what is posted on their site.

**Changes to the Terms of Service User Submissions Feedback**

Any feedback you submit to us will document certain personal information. Modern Commerce is committed to pleasing our visitors and encourages feedback. Your feedback allows us to understand your concerns and suggestions so improvements can be made.

**User Activity**

To monitor what areas of our site are being used least and most frequently Modern Commerce utilizes numerical data. Modern Commerce can better service you, the user, by recording the following data:

  * Your IP address 
  * The web browser you used 
  * Your internet service provider 
  * The time you visited our site 
  * What pages you viewed while on our site

**Cookies**

When you visit Modern Commerce, we assign your computer cookies to access our site and to personalize your user experience. With cookies, we are able to automatically collect information when you use our site. This includes information used for authentication purposes, storing site preferences and login information, so the user will not have to re-enter it each time he or she visits Modern Commerce. You may disable your use of cookies by following the instructions your browser, but this may limit your interaction with Modern Commerce significantly.

**Privacy Policy Terms and Changes**

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy as we see fit. If and when this happens, we will post the most updated version on this page. If there is ever a change in the way your personal information is used, you will be notified via email and this page.

**Information Transfer**

Modern Commerce does not sell or distribute your personal information to unaffiliated third parties unless, required by law, in response to a subpoena, court order, or similar investigative demand. We also may disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to protect our visitors, our employees, and the public.

Your information will never be sold, leased or transferred to any outside parties. Third party websites that work in partnership with us may have access to statistical information, but will never have access to your personal information. Information that is not personally identifiable may be used for marketing purposes.

Modern Commerce can transfer user information to our current or future affiliates. These affiliates include: our parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries or companies under common control. These companies are expected to follow Modern Commerce's privacy policy that is on this page.

Modern Commerce may hire third party companies to obtain statistical information about our users, like how many people clicked on a specific advertisement and the number of unique visitors on Modern Commerce. These statistics will help us optimize targeted advertisements and user content. This data will never include any personal information of our users.

**Advertising Links**

Modern Commerce may contain links to third-party websites that we are not affiliated with. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties and will not share your personal information with them. You are advised to read their privacy policies as well.

**Unsubscribe Information**

If at at any time you wish to unsubscribe from Modern Commerce mailing lists please let us know by visiting: <http://www.moderncommerce.com/unsubscribe>.

**Contacting Modern Commerce**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page.
